# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

Name: - ASFIYA ZAIN MANDEKAR

Email: - asfiyajuvale@yahoo.com

Contact No: - +971 543515443 (Primary) / +971 554135986 (WhatsApp)

Address: - 11a Rolla Street, Al Raffa, Bur Dubai, Dubai.



# **Objective:**

Wish to secure a position in the organization which gives me an opportunity to enhance my skills. Intend to contribute to the growth of the organization with best of my knowledge and experience to achieve organizational and personal excellence. Also, to be creative, innovative and adaptable enough so as to grow with the trend of technology.

# **Professional Summary:**

Insightful and results driven IT professional with 5 years of total experience.

2.5 years of experience working with IDBI Intech Ltd on Oracle and PL/SQL (April 2017 to Oct 2019)

2.5 years of experience working with Infosys Ltd on PL/SQL, Ab Initio and Unix. (Nov 2014 to March 2017)

# Work Experience: 1

Worked as "Executive Technology Delivery" with IDBI Intech Limited, Mumbai.

Project 1: EDW (Enterprise Data Warehouse) with IDBI Intech Limited				
Duration	April 2017 to October 2019.			
Skills	PL/SQL and Oracle			
Deceminations				

## Description:

IDBI Intech Ltd. is a wholly owned subsidiary IT Company of IDBI Bank Ltd. EDW is a bank's project and approach identified to have a centralized database system or data warehouse where all the required data from different sources would be made available on a single repository for access from different locations simultaneously.

# Role Played:

- Worked as PL/SQL developer in MIS department banking domain.
- Worked closely with Bank users for requirement gathering.
- Executing SQL queries for data fetching, updating and deleting.
- Worked on Microsoft Excel for different reports as per format.
- Reports extraction through UNIX and PL/SQL procedures.

Delivery of reports within timelines.

- Reports extraction through OTATA and TE/DQE procedures.
- Development of Ad hoc and fixed monthly based reports in Oracle.

Project 2: IDBI Federal Life Insurance (Onsite Project with IDBI Intech Limited)					
Duration	Dec 2018 till Feb 2019.				
Skills	PL/SQL and Oracle				
Description	): 				
IDBI Feder	IDBI Federal is Life Insurance company and a client of IDBI Intech Limited which handles the				
life insuran	ce activities and operations.				
Role Playe	d:				
•	I was working as a vendor resource for Development of Reports in Oracle database as				
	per client requirement.				
•	Worked closely with business users for gathering requirement.				

## Work Experience: 2

Worked as "Senior Operations Executive" with Infosys Limited, Pune.

Project: AMERICAN EXPRESS (with Infosys Limited)			
Duration	November 2014 to March 2017.		
Skills	Ab Initio, Unix and PL/SQL		
Descriptions			

Description:

The American Express Company, also known as Amex, is an American multinational financial services corporation. It is a financial company which today is known for its credit card business.

## Role Played:

- I was working as a Programmer and Ab Initio Admin for this project.
- Handled execution of different Ab Initio and UNIX commands for the migration of data across multiple servers.
- Creation of new sandboxes as per user requirements.
- Production Server Support with Administrative Tasks and PL/SQL support.
- Services implementation with use of monitoring tools SharePoint and Service Now.

#### **Technical Skills:**

Programming Languages	PL/SQL, Unix and Basics Unix Shell Scripting,	
Web Technologies	HTML.	
Other Technologies	VMware, vSphere and vCloud Automation.	
Tools	Ab Initio, Basic Tableau.	
DBMS	SQL Server, Oracle 9.	
IDE	Eclipse, Net beans, Microsoft Visual Studio and Toad (9.5).	
Job Functions	Requirement Gathering and Analysis, PL/SQL Development through Toad, Reports Extraction, Ab Initio Code Migration and Sandboxes creation and modification.	

# **Educational Qualification:**

SR.NO	COURSE	PASSINGYEAR	BOARD / UNIVERSITY	MARKS
1.	MSc.IT	2016-2018	Mumbai University	62 %
2.	BSc.IT	2011-2014	Mumbai University	76.23 %

#### **Achievements:**

## **Certification 1: External Certification**

### vSphere 6.0 Foundation

## **Description:**

It was an External Certification done in collaboration with Infosys Limited.

vSphere 6.0 imparted knowledge on Virtualization, vSphere ESXi and vCenter Server 6.0.

### **Certification 2: External Certification**

# VCP 6 (VMware Certified Professional 6 Cloud management and Automation)

#### **Description:**

It was an external certification done in collaboration with Infosys Limited.

VCP 6 imparted a deep knowledge on VMware Technology, Cloud management and Automation.

**Personal Details** 

Name: Asfiya Zain Mandekar **Date of Birth:** 04<sup>th</sup> December 1992

**Hobbies:** Music, Drawing, Travelling and Cooking, exploring new things.

Sports: Badminton, Dodge Ball.
Languages: Hindi, English, Marathi, Urdu.

Married. Married.

# **Declaration:**

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge And I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

(Asfiya Aslam Juvale)